My body... won't move!
I'll make you feel real good.
In exchange for your life force.
Damn you!
Who are you!?
I-It can't be...
Shima...
Episode 1: Chance Meeting
Yo, Asuno.
What's up?
You don't look so good.
Ookubo, yesterday, I...
Never mind. It's nothing.
I know exactly how you feel.
Picking out the cutest girl in our class isn't easy at all.
What?
Someone proper like Fuzuki isn't bad,
but there's only one thing that makes a girl.
I mean, Kanae's totally stacked!
I couldn't care less!
I need a good part-time job.
You got fired?
Such is the power of recession.
Man, you don't have any luck at all.
It's bad enough that you have to live by yourself.
Not to mention my parents taking my luck into the negatives.
We're going to Europe for some training.
I'm sure you'll be fine by yourself, Shin-chan.
They weren't sending me much money before,
and now it's even less.
I won't be able to pay rent if I keep sitting around like this.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Are you okay?
S-Sorry.
No, it's fine.
I wasn't watching where I was going.
Ouch!
Sorry, I didn't mean to.
N-No worries.
See you later.
Huh?
Cute, isn't she?
That's Shimazu Sakuya from Class 1.
She's pretty as a doll.
I heard her family's rich too.
You sure know a lot about her.
She's got a lot of fans.
But I think her upper regions here could use a little boost...
I still couldn't care any less.
The bigger, the better.
They hold the hopes and dreams of men!
Sure.
I'll give you a permission slip once you figure out where you're going to work.
Thank you, Sensei.
So, what type of job are you looking for?
I was thinking a kitchen or...
What are you doing?
Sorry, I can't help myself whenever I see a mess.
Now, that's rude.
This is the best my desk has ever looked.
Seriously?
So you can cook, huh?
And you like cleaning too...
Why don't you marry me?
The pay's good.
I don't think that's a job...
Not to worry.
I've got the perfect job for you.
Chemistry Prep Room
She duped me.
She's so lazy, she gets her students to clean for her.
She'd even make a cat clean for her if she could.
Wow. Nice timing.
No fair.
I guess that'll do it.
Hey! What's going on!?
A-Asano-kun...
Hey! Wake up!
W-What happened here?
I don't know.
We were just passing by,
and she was just lying there...
What's that?
W-We're alive...
Wait.
Never mind us.
Everyone else is in danger.
Where are you going?
Get her to the hospital, quick!
Damn it.
Where did it go?
Somebody help me!
I don't know who you are,
but could you help me, please?
I'll definitely repay you.
Y-You don't have to!
Did you see this huge monster move by here—
Could you pull this out?
I can't do it...
Who would do something like this?
Wh-What was that?
Hurry! Please pull it out!
There you go.
You should be fine now—
Shimazu-san?
You idiot!
The hell did you just do!?
What? She was—
I finally caught her too!
A bow...
Did you shoot this arrow?
I did!
You absolute jerk!
What are you thinking?
Why would you shoot at a girl like this with a bow?
She's not human.
Huh?
Now, get out of the way.
I haven't done anything!
I'm not falling for that!
W-Wait!
What?
You're in my way!
B-But...
I'm innocent!
Shut up!
Stop it!
I'll shoot you too if you don't move out of the way.
She's just a girl!
Does that look like a girl to you?
You tire me, little Shimazu.
See you later, my boy.
Thanks for the help.
You won't escape!
W-What was that?
This is your fault.
You're the one who ran into me this morning, aren't you?
Asano Shinichirou!
How do you know my name?
I never forget the names and faces of my enemies.
E-Enemies?
What are you looking at, you pervert!?
I even cast magic on that arrow so it couldn't be removed.
So how did you pull it out?
Answer me now!
Come on!
You nearly choked me to death.
Too bad I didn't.
Hey...
I've placed a barrier around the school, so it couldn't have ran that far.
We're going after it.
Wait, me too?
Well, of course!
You owe me, you know.
I still don't get why...
Who do you think saved you last night?
I hate people who don't repay someone for their good deeds.
So what was up with that cat and centipede?
They're specters.
Specters?
Youkai, ghosts...
They have plenty of names.
They rise from the world of the dead...
A world completely separate from this one.
But none of them belong here in our realm.
They attack and steal people's life force in order for them to stay here.
It's been my family's duty
to capture and seal specters since the Kamakura era.
I'm the 37th head of the Shimazu family.
And the name's Shimazu Sakuya.
That nekomata is bound to attack someone again.
We need to seal her before she does.
Then we need to get the other students out of here.
We're the only ones left in the school.
Huh?
I told you. I put up a barrier.
Normal humans can't bear to stay inside.
Then what does that make me?
Yeah...
I'm not sure.
Well, not like it matters.
You're awfully carefree about this...
I hope Matsuura-san and the others are okay.
I'm sure Fuzuki and the others are just fine.
I asked Nadeshiko to help.
The teacher!?
Shh! She's here.
Where!?
Music Room
Sh-Shimazu-san...
So she's...
over there?
Just shoot already, Shimazu-san!
Don't just stand there! We're going after her!
Over here.
Your shot did that?
Looks like it.
I won't let her get away this time.
I knew it was you.
Was that really you?
N-No! It wasn't me!
This scary thing suddenly attacked me and—
Drop the pitiful act, nekomata.
H-Hold on!
Trying to get in my way again?
That's not it!
Take a look at her arm.
Claw marks?
That's it! That thing did it!
That's my arrow...
What is that monster?
A raijuu?
A specter that controls lightning.
It's very strong.
Strong?
How strong?
A low five in the spirit hierarchy.
Low five?
I'm saying that specter's super rare.
Hardly anyone sees them in the human world.
What's it doing here then?
I don't know.
It shouldn't have been able to get through the gate so easily...
But what I do know
is that if we don't take it down, we're toast.
D-Did you see?
Is this really the time for that!?
Now I'm pissed!
Shimazu Style Spirit Bow Technique:
Tsumuha!
You got it!
What?
I-It's getting bigger...
It's absorbing electricity.
What should we do?
How about we talk to it like we did with the nekomata?
Don't be stupid.
Just look at its eyes.
It's gone mad.
It won't listen to us at all like that.
Shimazu-san!
Ouch...
Y-You...
Do that again and I'll kill you!
Why me...
Why are you two flirting right now?
How is this flirting!?
Aren't you a Shimazu?
Go take revenge for me and kill it already!
Can it, you!
Why don't you do it yourself!?
Yeah, why don't I?
You are so useless.
Hey, hang in there!
I-I'm fine.
I'm the head of the Shimazu family.
I can't lose this battle.
Shimazu Style Spirit Bow Technique:
Tsumugare!
|
Shimazu Style Spirit Bow Technique:
Murasame!
|
It can't be...
Shimazu-san!
No...
Shimazu-san?
It's taking her life force away
in exchange for the ultimate pleasure.
That's...
Stop...
I have to do something.
A human can't do anything!
Shimazu, run while you can!
Shinichirou!
How can you be so reckless?
Maybe I am, but...
I couldn't just leave you there.
I can't...
You're...
Well, you did save my life, my boy.
You really are nice.
What are you doing!?
Huh? What was...
That was my first kiss too...
Even though my life forced got sucked out...
What's happening?
I feel power welling up...
I don't get what's going on,
but I've got you now!
Prepare to die!
Shinichirou, lend me your jacket.
Things are going to be a little different this time.
A bow of any wood, be it catalpa, spindle, or zelkova,
recedes when the arrow is fired.
Send this spirit home.
Shimazu Style Spirit Bow Final Technique:
Habakiri!
|
Raijuu, may you rest within this land.
Shimazu!
Don't look, you pervert!
I-I'm sorry!
So, did you get it?
No, all I could do was seal it to make it stop moving.
To send back something as powerful as a raijuu, you need to know its true name.
True name?
Looks like things are settled here.
You're...
Thanks for helping out.
I was just repaying my debt to you.
Looks like things cleared up between us too,
so I'll be leaving now.
That won't be happening.
H-Hey!
What are you doing!?
Episode 1 - Fin -
See you next time!